Continuing Studies fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Non-credit programs, 1986 - 1999; F-94-4; 94 cm of textual records 11 photographs 2 contact sheets; Physical description: 11 photographs located in F-94-4-3-1-9
  - Applied Sciences Continuing Education Program, 1989 - 1999; F-94-4-1; 34 cm of textual records
    - General programs, 1989 - 1998; F-94-4-1-1; 5 cm of textual records
      - Written Communications Course (in-house Epson), 1998; F-94-4-1-1-16 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Building Strategic Alliances, 1998; F-94-4-1-1-17 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
    - Computer programming courses, 1990 - 1999; F-94-4-1-2; 12 cm of textual records
      - QuickChip workshop, 1990; F-94-4-1-2-1 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Advanced C Language Programming: Data Structures and Program Organization, 1990; F-94-4-1-2-2 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Understanding Local Area Networks, 1990 - 1991; F-94-4-1-2-3 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Introduction to Object Oriented Programming with C++, 1995 - 1996; F-94-4-1-2-4 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Introduction to Object Oriented Programming with C++, 1996; F-94-4-1-2-5 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Advanced C++ Programming, 1996; F-94-4-1-2-6 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Introduction to C++ Programming, 1996; F-94-4-1-2-7 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Programming in the Microsoft Windows NT 4.0 Environment, 1997; F-94-4-1-2-8 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Managing the Software Development Process, 1997; F-94-4-1-2-9 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Introduction to C++ Programming, 1997; F-94-4-1-2-10 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Advanced C++ Programming, 1997; F-94-4-1-2-11 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Distributed Object Systems Using CORBA, 1997; F-94-4-1-2-12 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Introduction to Perl Programming, 1997; F-94-4-1-2-13 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Basic Java Programming, 1997; F-94-4-1-2-14 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Object Oriented Analysis and Design, 1997; F-94-4-1-2-15 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Introduction to Object Oriented Programming with C++, 1997; F-94-4-1-2-16 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Graphical User Interface Design, 1997; F-94-4-1-2-17 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Managing the Software Development Process, 1997; F-94-4-1-2-18 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Introduction to Object Oriented Concepts, 1997; F-94-4-1-2-19 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Object Oriented Analysis and Design, 1997 - 1998; F-94-4-1-2-20 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Advanced C++ Programming, 1997 - 1998; F-94-4-1-2-21 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Developing Object Oriented Windows Applications, 1997 - 1998; F-94-4-1-2-22 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Introduction to Unix, 1998; F-94-4-1-2-23 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Introduction to Perl Programming (in-house Northern Telecom), 1998; F-94-4-1-2-24 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Introduction to C++ Programming, 1998; F-94-4-1-2-25 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Object Oriented Analysis and Design, 1998; F-94-4-1-2-26 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Introduction to Object Oriented Programming with C++, 1998; F-94-4-1-2-27 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Advanced C++ Programming with Design Patterns, 1998; F-94-4-1-2-28 (Archival box - standard 94-32)
      - Object Oriented Analysis and Design, 1999; F-94-4-1-2-29 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
      - Java Primer, 1999; F-94-4-1-2-30 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
      - Introduction to Programming Using C, 1999; F-94-4-1-2-31 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
      - Communications Technology Overview, 1999; F-94-4-1-2-32 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
      - Introduction to C++ Programming, 1999; F-94-4-1-2-33 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
      - Object Oriented Primer, 1999; F-94-4-1-2-34 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
      - Linux System Administration, 1999; F-94-4-1-2-35 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
      - Linux in the Office, 1999; F-94-4-1-2-36 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
      - Linux and Open Source Overview, 1999; F-94-4-1-2-37 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
    - The Institute for Government Informatics Professionals, 1993 - 1995; F-94-4-1-3; 2 cm of textual records
      - Introduction to Data Communications, 1993 - 1994; F-94-4-1-3-1 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
      - Course materials, 1993 - 1994; F-94-4-1-3-2 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
      - Regional Council, 1994; F-94-4-1-3-3 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
      - Introduction to Data Communications, 1994 - 1995; F-94-4-1-3-4 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
      - Correspondence and working papers, 1994 - 1995; F-94-4-1-3-5 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
    - International programs, 1993 - 1999; F-94-4-1-4; 3 cm of textual records
      - Seoul National University programs, 1993 - 1995; F-94-4-1-4-1 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
      - Doing Business in North America (Hanjin Shipping Ltd., Korea), 1994; F-94-4-1-4-2 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
      - Environmental Management: Theory and Methods (Korea Water Resources/KOWACO), 1995; F-94-4-1-4-3 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
      - Management Techniques in North America (Hanjin Shipping Ltd., Korea), 1995; F-94-4-1-4-4 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
      - Cross Cultural Orientation in the North American Environment (Hansol Paper Ltd., Korea), 1996; F-94-4-1-4-5 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
      - Management Techniques in North America (Hanjin Shipping Ltd., Korea), 1996 - 1997; F-94-4-1-4-6 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
      - EDI Taxation and Technology Transfer (Dept. of Revenue, Thailand), 1997; F-94-4-1-4-7 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
      - Management Techniques in North America (Hanjin Shipping Ltd., Korea), 1999; F-94-4-1-4-8 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
    - Internet program, 1994 - 1995; F-94-4-1-5; 3 cm of textual records
      - Introduction to the Internet, 1994; F-94-4-1-5-1 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
      - Internet Program - Communicating Over the Internet, 1994; F-94-4-1-5-2 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
      - Internet Program - Connecting to the Internet, 1994; F-94-4-1-5-3 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
      - Internet Program, 1994 - 1995; F-94-4-1-5-4 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
      - Using the Internet, 1994 - 1995; F-94-4-1-5-5 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
      - Internet Program for Writers and Publishers, 1995; F-94-4-1-5-6 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
      - Using the Internet Program, 1995; F-94-4-1-5-7 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
      - Internet Program - development, 1995; F-94-4-1-5-8 (Archival box - standard 94-33)
    - Project Management program, 1991 - 1999; F-94-4-1-6; 5 cm of textual records
      - Project Management, 1991; F-94-4-1-6-1 (Archival box - standard 94-34)
      - Project Management, 1992 - 1993; F-94-4-1-6-2 (Archival box - standard 94-34)
      - Project Management, 1994; F-94-4-1-6-3 (Archival box - standard 94-34)
      - Project Management (in-house Forintek Canada Corp.), 1994 - 1995; F-94-4-1-6-4 (Archival box - standard 94-34)
      - Project Management, 1995; F-94-4-1-6-5 (Archival box - standard 94-34)
      - Project Managers Workshop (Samsung), 1995; F-94-4-1-6-6 (Archival box - standard 94-34)
      - Project Management, 1996; F-94-4-1-6-7 (Archival box - standard 94-34)
      - Project Management, 1997; F-94-4-1-6-8 (Archival box - standard 94-34)
      - Project Management, 1998; F-94-4-1-6-9 (Archival box - standard 94-34)
      - Project Management, 1999; F-94-4-1-6-10 (Archival box - standard 94-34)
    - Risk Assessment and Decision Analysis for Management of Natural Resources, 1995 - 1999; F-94-4-1-7; 2 cm of textual records
      - Correspondence and working papers, 1995; F-94-4-1-7-1 (Archival box - standard 94-34)
      - In-house program for Timber Supply Branch, Ministry of Forests, 1996; F-94-4-1-7-2 (Archival box - standard 94-34)
      - In-house program for Strategic Fisheries, BC Hydro, 1998 - 1999; F-94-4-1-7-3 (Archival box - standard 94-34)
    - Technology Industries Association (TIA), 1994 - 1995; F-94-4-1-8; 2 cm of textual records
      - TIA/SFU Business Program - development, 1994 - 1995; F-94-4-1-8-1 (Archival box - standard 94-34)
      - TIA/SFU Business Program - course outlines, 1994 - 1995; F-94-4-1-8-2 (Archival box - standard 94-34)
      - TIA/SFU Business Program - evaluations, 1995; F-94-4-1-8-3 (Archival box - standard 94-34)
  - B.C. Tel CTI Convergence course, 1987 - 1997; F-94-4-2; 14 cm of textual records
    In August 1988 the British Columbia Telephone Company entered into agreement with SFU for the delivery of a Certificate Program in Telecommunications Engineering. The specialized program, developed to upgrade the technical knowledge of BC Tel professional engineers in telecommunications technologies, was jointly run by SFU and the University of California at Los Angeles (UCLA) and managed by the Applied Sciences Program in Continuing Studies. Working in collaboration with the BC Tel Engineering Training Committee, Continuing Studies developed a series of eight, one-week extensive courses that covered topics such as communication systems, digital concepts, voice networks, communication standards and ISDN. Courses were made up of a combination of lectures, technical presentations, laboratories, and group activities. Each course had a coordinator rather than a single instructor and industry experts were brought in to give presentations. At the end of each session, courses were evaluated by participants and individuals outside of the BC Tel/SFU-UCLA group to ensure that participants acquired an in-depth understanding of changing technology and communication systems.
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the development and administration of the BC Tel Convergence course program. Activities, events and topics documented include BC Tel's initial request for proposal, course development, progress reports, instructors contracts and promotional materials sent out to BC Tel staff. Records include correspondence, working papers, reports, course outlines and evaluations, contracts, budgets and financial working papers, and pamphlets.
    - BC Tel - curriculum, 1987; F-94-4-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 94-34)
    - BC Tel - planning documents, 1989 - 1991; F-94-4-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 94-34)
    - BC Tel - instructor's contracts, 1989 - 1991; F-94-4-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 94-34)
    - BC Tel - proposal/contract, 1993 - 1995; F-94-4-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 94-34)
    - BC Tel - promotion, 1994; F-94-4-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 94-34)
    - BC Tel Technical Staff - block A evaluations, 1994 - 1995; F-94-4-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 94-34)
    - BC Tel Technical Staff - block B evaluations, 1994 - 1995; F-94-4-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 94-34)
    - BC Tel Technical Staff - block C evaluations, 1994 - 1995; F-94-4-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 94-35)
    - BC Tel Convergence - correspondence, 1995; F-94-4-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 94-35)
    - BC Tel Convergence- proposal/contract, 1995 - 1996; F-94-4-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 94-35)
    - BC Tel Convergence - development, 1995 - 1996; F-94-4-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 94-35)
    - BC Tel Convergence - evaluations: Regulatory Matters, 1996; F-94-4-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 94-35)
    - BC Tel Convergence - C. Murray correspondence, 1996; F-94-4-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 94-35)
    - Computer Telephony Integration - course evaluation, 1996; F-94-4-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 94-35)
    - BC Tel Convergence - instructors, 1996; F-94-4-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 94-35)
    - BC Tel Convergence - signed contracts/BFRF, 1996; F-94-4-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 94-35)
    - BC Tel - 1 day Computer Telephony Integration courses, 1996; F-94-4-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 94-35)
    - BC Tel Convergence - evaluation D1, 1996; F-94-4-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 94-35)
    - BC Tel Convergence - evaluation D2, 1996; F-94-4-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 94-35)
    - BC Tel Convergence - evaluation D3, 1996; F-94-4-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 94-35)
    - BC Tel Convergence - evaluation D4, 1996; F-94-4-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 94-35)
    - BC Tel Convergence - evaluation E1, 1996; F-94-4-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 94-35)
    - BC Tel Convergence - evaluation E2, 1996; F-94-4-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 94-35)
    - BC Tel Convergence - evaluation E3, 1996; F-94-4-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 94-35)
    - BC Tel Convergence - evaluation D5, 1997; F-94-4-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 94-35)
    - BC Tel Convergence - evaluation D6, 1997; F-94-4-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 94-35)
  - Management Skills in Advanced Technology (MSAT) program, 1986 - 1998; F-94-4-3; 46 cm of textual records 11 photographs 2 contact sheets
    The Management Skills in Advanced Technology Program (MSAT) was established in 1986 after a series of development seminars with employers, managers, and engineers in science and technology-based industries identified the need for a management skills training program. The President's Fund provided a loan to the Applied Sciences Continuing Studies program in order to get to the program started and soon after its inception, it was recognized as an innovative program in professional development education winning a Canadian Association for University Continuing Education Distinctive Program Award in 1989. The design of the program has changed little since the development of core courses in the late 1980's that include Managing Technology, Engineering Economics and Financial Planning, and Project Management. Students - comprised mainly of engineers, software developers, technologists and scientists seeking to develop their management skills - receive twenty-four days of instruction over a six month period in two three-day modules. Resource persons from the community are brought in as guest speakers. Through lectures, exercises, and group assignments students cover topics including human and organizational behaviour, resource allocation, demand forecasting, economic and financial analysis, project management, sales and marketing, production, operations, business planning, writing and public speaking. The program culminates with a team business planning project using a local technology company as a case example. As of 2005, the program consists of eight integrated core courses and includes new topics relevant to modern industry demands such as eBusiness.
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the development and administration of the Management Skills in Advanced Technology Program. Activities, events and topics documented include program planning and general administration, instructors workshops and meetings, course and instructor evaluations, and graduation ceremonies. Records also include those relating to core courses of the program such as Communications Skills; Economic and Financial Planning; Implementing Management Concepts in Advanced Technology; Managing Creative Technically-Oriented People; Project Management; and feasibility planning for MSAT II courses. Records include correspondence, working papers, minutes, course outlines, student binders, budget and financial working papers, pamphlets, photographs and contact sheets.
    - Program administration, 1986 - 1996; F-94-4-3-1; 31 cm of textual records 11 photographs 2 contact sheets
      - Program administration, 1986 - 1987; F-94-4-3-1-1 (Archival box - standard 94-35)
      - Advisory Committee, 1987; F-94-4-3-1-2 (Archival box - standard 94-35)
      - Management Skills - delivery, 1987 - 1988; F-94-4-3-1-3 (Archival box - standard 94-35)
      - Program administration, 1987 - 1988; F-94-4-3-1-4 (Archival box - standard 94-35)
      - Program budget, 1987 - 1988; F-94-4-3-1-5 (Archival box - standard 94-36)
      - Program development, 1987 - 1988; F-94-4-3-1-6 (Archival box - standard 94-36)
      - Advisory Committee, 1988; F-94-4-3-1-7 (Archival box - standard 94-36)
      - Management Skills in Advanced Technology - workshop planning, 1988; F-94-4-3-1-8 (Archival box - standard 94-36)
      - MSAT class photos, 1988 - 1996; F-94-4-3-1-9 (Archival box - small 94-44)
        Textual records; Photographic materials
      - Advisory Committee, 1989 - 1996; F-94-4-3-1-10 (Archival box - standard 94-36)
      - Instructors meetings, 1990; F-94-4-3-1-11 (Archival box - standard 94-36)
      - MSAT blank certificate, 1990; F-94-4-3-1-12 (Archival box - standard 94-36)
      - Program development, 1990; F-94-4-3-1-13 (Archival box - standard 94-36)
      - Instructor correspondence, 1990 - 1991; F-94-4-3-1-14 (Archival box - standard 94-36)
      - Program planning, 1990 - 1991; F-94-4-3-1-15 (Archival box - standard 94-36)
      - Graduation, 1991; F-94-4-3-1-16 (Archival box - standard 94-36)
      - Management Skills - case study, 1991; F-94-4-3-1-17 (Archival box - standard 94-36)
      - Focus Session - Managing Technology, 1991 - 1992; F-94-4-3-1-18 (Archival box - standard 94-36)
      - Graduation, 1991 - 1992; F-94-4-3-1-19 (Archival box - standard 94-36)
      - Instructors, 1991 - 1992; F-94-4-3-1-20 (Archival box - standard 94-36)
      - MSAT program student binder, 1991 - 1992; F-94-4-3-1-21 (Archival box - standard 94-36)
      - Advanced Systems Institute (ASI), 1991 - 1995; F-94-4-3-1-22 (Archival box - standard 94-36)
      - Program planning, 1992; F-94-4-3-1-23 (Archival box - standard 94-36)
      - Strategic planning panel session, 1992; F-94-4-3-1-24 (Archival box - standard 94-36)
      - Instructors, 1992 - 1993; F-94-4-3-1-25 (Archival box - standard 94-36)
      - MSAT student binder, 1992 - 1993; F-94-4-3-1-26 (Archival box - standard 94-36)
      - Graduation, 1993; F-94-4-3-1-27 (Archival box - standard 94-36)
      - Promotion, 1993; F-94-4-3-1-28 (Archival box - standard 94-37)
      - Instructors correspondence and meetings, 1993 - 1994; F-94-4-3-1-29 (Archival box - standard 94-37)
      - MSAT program student binder, 1993 - 1994; F-94-4-3-1-30 (Archival box - standard 94-37)
      - Instructors meetings, 1993 - 1995; F-94-4-3-1-31 (Archival box - standard 94-37)
      - Graduation, 1994; F-94-4-3-1-32 (Archival box - standard 94-37)
      - Strategic planning panel session, 1994; F-94-4-3-1-33 (Archival box - standard 94-37)
      - Instructors payments, 1994 - 1995; F-94-4-3-1-34 (Archival box - standard 94-37)
      - MSAT program student binder, 1994 - 1995; F-94-4-3-1-35 (Archival box - standard 94-37)
      - Correspondence, 1995; F-94-4-3-1-36 (Archival box - standard 94-37)
      - Graduation, 1995; F-94-4-3-1-37 (Archival box - standard 94-37)
      - Training Needs workshop, 1995; F-94-4-3-1-38 (Archival box - standard 94-37)
      - Instructors payments, 1995 - 1996; F-94-4-3-1-39 (Archival box - standard 94-37)
      - Graduation, 1996; F-94-4-3-1-40 (Archival box - standard 94-37)
      - Instructors meetings, 1996; F-94-4-3-1-41 (Archival box - standard 94-37)
      - Program administration, 1996; F-94-4-3-1-42 (Archival box - standard 94-37)
    - Program evaluations, 1987 - 1995; F-94-4-3-2; 4 cm of textual records
      - Management Skills - evaluation, 1987 - 1988; F-94-4-3-2-1 (Archival box - standard 94-37)
      - Management Skills - evaluations, 1988 - 1989; F-94-4-3-2-2 (Archival box - standard 94-37)
      - Program evaluations, 1988 - 1989; F-94-4-3-2-3 (Archival box - standard 94-37)
      - Management Skills - evaluations, 1989 - 1990; F-94-4-3-2-4 (Archival box - standard 94-37)
      - Management Skills - evaluations, 1990 - 1991; F-94-4-3-2-5 (Archival box - standard 94-37)
      - Management Skills - evaluations, 1991; F-94-4-3-2-6 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Evaluations - summarized, 1991 - 1992; F-94-4-3-2-7 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Management Skills - evaluations, 1992 - 1993; F-94-4-3-2-8 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Evaluations - summarized, 1993; F-94-4-3-2-9 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Evaluations - summarized, 1994 - 1995; F-94-4-3-2-10 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
    - Communications Skills courses, 1988 - 1996; F-94-4-3-3; 2 cm of textual records
      - Communication Skills - session 1, 1988; F-94-4-3-3-1 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Communication Skills, 1990 - 1991; F-94-4-3-3-2 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Communication Skills (Written), 1992; F-94-4-3-3-3 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Oral Communication Skills, 1994; F-94-4-3-3-4 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Communication Skills (Written), 1995; F-94-4-3-3-5 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Communication Skills (Written), 1996; F-94-4-3-3-6 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Communication Skills (Oral), 1996; F-94-4-3-3-7 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
    - Economic and Financial Planning courses, 1987 - 1996; F-94-4-3-4; 3 cm of textual records
      - Economic and Financial Planning, 1987 - 1988; F-94-4-3-4-1 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Economic and Financial Planning, 1988 - 1989; F-94-4-3-4-2 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Economic and Financial Planning, 1989 - 1990; F-94-4-3-4-3 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Economic and Financial Planning, 1990 - 1991; F-94-4-3-4-4 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Business Plan Development and Presentation, 1992; F-94-4-3-4-5 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Business plan development schedule, 1992 - 1993; F-94-4-3-4-6 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Business Plan Development and Presentation, 1993; F-94-4-3-4-7 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Business Plan Development and Presentation, 1994; F-94-4-3-4-8 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Engineering Economics and Financial Planning, 1994; F-94-4-3-4-9 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Business Plan Development and Presentation, 1995; F-94-4-3-4-10 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Engineering Economics, 1995 - 1996; F-94-4-3-4-11 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Business Plan Development and Presentation, 1996; F-94-4-3-4-12 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
    - Implementing Management Concepts in Advanced Technology courses, 1987 - 1996; F-94-4-3-5; 4 cm of textual records
      - Implementing Management Concepts in Advanced Technology, 1987 - 1988; F-94-4-3-5-1 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Implementing Management Concepts in Advanced Technology, 1988 - 1989; F-94-4-3-5-2 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Managing Technology, 1989; F-94-4-3-5-3 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Implementing Management Concepts in Advanced Technology, 1989 - 1990; F-94-4-3-5-4 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Implementing Management Concepts in Advanced Technology, 1990; F-94-4-3-5-5 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Managing Technology, 1993; F-94-4-3-5-6 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Design For and Managing Production, 1993; F-94-4-3-5-7 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Designing For and Managing Production, 1994; F-94-4-3-5-8 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Strategic Planning and Marketing, 1994; F-94-4-3-5-9 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Designing For and Managing Operations, 1994 - 1995; F-94-4-3-5-10 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Strategic Planning and Marketing, 1995; F-94-4-3-5-11 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Managing Technology, 1995; F-94-4-3-5-12 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Design For and Managing Production, 1996; F-94-4-3-5-13 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Managing Technology, 1996; F-94-4-3-5-14 (Archival box - standard 94-38)